# Ryan (Yu-Lin) Chung

## Game Programmer / VFX Artist / Graphic Designer

## **Professional Summary**

Game programmer with two years of experience. Specializing in C# .NET, C++ development, seeking a position in which my adaptable programming skills can be utilized, reinforced and improved in an outstanding workplace.

Graphic designer and VFX artist involved in commercial productions with eight year experience.

Melbourne, VIC

0416-146-703

□ ryan@alpacagamedev.com

nttps://alpacagamedev.com

# CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- Adept knowledge and use of C# in Unity and C++ for game development
- Experience in tool creation in Unity for the team to utilize in produciton
- Perseverance and determination to accomplish assigned tasks
- Coordination to work as a part of the team to achieve goals
- Flexibility to learn new skills / tools and apply to work
- Prominent creativity to generate solutions to the problems
- Adaptability to work in a creative and fast paced environment

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Wildcat Industries (Aust) Pty., Ltd.

Graphic Designer / Web Designer / Social Media Marketing Feb 2013 - Dec 2017 in Melbourne, VIC

- Responsible for various types of graphic design, including flyers, web design, demonstration filmmaking

#### ShinJyh Communication Co., LTD

Motion Graphic Artist / Assistant Film Editor

Dec 2010 - Mar 2011 in Taipei, TAIWAN

- Responsible for various types of post-production, including editing, motion graphic design, and sound effect adjustment
- Matte extraction and compositing in the production pipeline

#### Azamawa Vision Design

Web Designer / Graphic Designer Jan 2010 - Dec 2010 in Kaohsiung, TAIWAN

- Responsible for various types of graphic design, including flyers, web design

#### Fareastern Animation

Character Animation, Rigging Leader / Modeler / Texture Artist Physics Simulation Leader / Layout Artist / Compositing Artist Apr 2009 - Dec 2009 in Taipei, TAIWAN

- Responsible for most types of work in animation, including modeling, texturing, rigging, animation, lighting, rendering and compositing
- Autodesk Maya nCloth/Hair based simulation and troubleshooting
- Character animation and rigging team leader

## Global Star Trading Co., LTD

Game UI Designer / Motion Graphic Artist Aug 2008 - Apr 2009 in Taipei, TAIWAN

- Responsible for most types of 3D/2D motion/still graphic design, including gambling arcade video game UI design, billboard motion graphic design and arcade machine appearance design.
- ★ Motion Graphic / Animation Showreel https://vimeo.com/ryan0432

# SKILL SET

HTML5

CSS3

Photoshop Illustrator

After Effects

Teamwork

Troubleshooting

Self-supervision

Communication

Creativity

Emotional Intelligence

# **EDUCATION**

### Academy of Interactive Entertainment

Adv. Diploma of Game Development - Game Programming Feb 2017 - Dec 2018 in Melbourne, VIC

Specializing in C++, C# in Unity and Mircosoft Visual Studio. Through the course, I have learned from the basics of data structure, the core programming skills and conventions to using that knowledge to build a custom game engine in C++. I have also become experienced working in a small team environment, following the industry standard to build goal oriented tools for the team in C# Unity. Accomplished a puzzleplatformer game with 4 fellow students (1 other programmer, 2 artists, 1 designer) for the final project.

## Min-Chuan University

Bachelor of Arts - Digital Media Design

Sep 2002 - Jul 2006 in Taoyuan, TAIWAN

Specializing in various graphic design and 3D software. Through the course, I have learned the knowledge and skills from basics of design, chromatology to cinematic photography, storyboard creation and idea realization through 3D/2D animation. Accomplished a 3D animated short with 3 fellow students as the director and character animator in the team.

# REFEREES

## Matt Dodd

Academy of Interactive Entertainment Mobile: 0433-809-433, Email: matthewd@aie.edu.au

#### Jon Flynn

Wildcat Industries (Aust) Pty., Ltd.

Mobile: 0419-321-495, Email: sales@wildcatindustries.com.au

#### Karim Turbez

Benlai Pictures (Shanghai), Animated Film Director Mobile: (886) 928-786-314, Email: karimturbez@gmail.com